(Sheldon:)Wolowitz is trying to outflank us.
(Sheldon:)Let out some string, add altitude,
I'll go under and cut his line.
(Leonard:)Why wouldn't Penny
want her friends to meet me?
(Sheldon:)Focus, Leonard, focus.
(Sheldon:)The heat of battle is upon us.
The dogs of war are unleashed.
(Leonard:)Maybe Koothrappali's right,
maybe I embarrass her.
(Sheldon:)You're embarrassing me.
(Sheldon:)A grown man worrying
about such nonsense.
We're in the middle of flying kites.
(Sheldon:)-Sorry.
-Sorry won't bring their kites down.
Ouch! String burn. String burn.
(Raj:)Oh, they think we're flanking.
They're playing right into our hands.
At the count of three,
we execute the flying scissor.
-One, two, thre--
-Whoa.
(Howard:)-You see that?
-See what?
(Howard:)-That chick. She smiled at me.
-No, she didn't.
(Raj:)-She did.
-Come on, scissors, scissors.
(Howard:)-Hold my line.
-What? I can't scissors by myself.
Howard, come back!
SHELDON:
Victory!